**PRIVACY POLICY**

**Stealth Ops 99 – PRIVACY POLICY**

**This is the Privacy Policy for Stealth Ops 99 LLC. and this Website tactical.stealthops99.com (individually and collectively the “Company”). When you use this Website, you agree to the Privacy Policy that follows. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy you should immediately stop using this Website.**

**Information The Company Collects**

**The Company is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors. Accordingly, the Company does not collect personally-identifying information from users unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. The Company does not share any information with anyone outside our company. The Company only collects personal details to give customers access to the services of this Website, for email communication with an option to opt-out, and for billing purposes.**

**When you visit the Website, your browser automatically sends us an IP (Internet Protocol) address and certain other information (including the type of browser you use). The Company may use this IP address and other information to give you access to the Website and otherwise administer the Website. In certain parts of the Website, the Company may ask you to provide your name or other information so that the Company can provide you with information you request, consider your application for registering with us, or take other action indicated in the part of the Website where the information is requested. You are under no obligation to provide us with this information, but without it, the Company may not be able to take the action requested. The Website also includes features that allow communication by electronic mail or otherwise.**

**If you choose to use these features, you will be required to provide us your e-mail address and other personally-identifying information (such as your name or street address) the Company may deem necessary in order to communicate with you electronically or otherwise.**

**When you provide any personally identifying information to us, you acknowledge that you are knowingly and voluntarily providing us the information. The Company will not use such information for marketing purposes, but the Company may respond to the electronic mail messages you send us, take other action indicated in the part of the Website where the information is requested, and use such information for any other business purpose, including sending you subsequent communications concerning this Website, or our company’s products and services.**

**You also should be aware that the Company collects certain usage information about the Website, such as the number and frequency of visitors to certain parts of the Website. This data is used only in the aggregate and does not include any personally identifying information. The Company also uses information in a number of anonymous or aggregated forms that do not identify individuals for the general management, marketing and improvement of our business.**

**The information collected is never revealed, sold, or made public for any reason. Personally identifiable information provided by subscribers (name, email or home address, etc.) is never disclosed to any individual or business unless you have authorized us to do so or unless the Company is required by law or the Company has a good faith basis for believing that you are in violation of this Privacy Policy, our Terms and Conditions, or applicable laws.**

**How the Company uses information**

**The Company uses personally identifiable information to undertake such activities as:**

**Communicate with you according to the preferences you have told us. Monitor and improve our business and use of the Website. Endeavor to prevent and address any possible fraud or misuse of our services. Ensure compliance with any relevant legislation.**

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

**Like many companies, the Company uses "cookie" and/or “web beacon” technologies on the Website. Cookies may tell us whether you have visited the Website before or are a new visitor. Web Beacons are tags that can monitor the behavior of a user visiting the Website or sending an e-mail.**

**Each time a subscriber logs into the Website, the Company stores a temporary 'cookie' in the browser files of that subscriber's computer. This cookie is used during your online session to allow you free access to the Website, and to store basket contents, without repeatedly requiring you to re-enter your user name and password. When you log off or leave the Website, the cookies file is automatically removed.**

**The cookies the Company uses do not collect any personally identifying information about you or provide us with any way to contact you, and the cookies do not extract any information from your computer. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. Each browser is different; so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. However, you must enable cookies from the Website in order to use most functions on the Website.**

**Information recorded through web beacons is used to report anonymous individual and/or aggregate information about our users. Aggregate information may include demographic and usage information. No personally identifiable information about you is shared with partners or third parties from this research. You may choose to opt-out of our using this information.**

**Advertising Policy**

**This product (and all other products by Stealth Ops 99 LLC) are advertised online and offline in various media outlets. You may see our ads on Facebook, Google, Bing, Yahoo, Taboola, Content.ad and various other online advertising providers. Web viewers may be tracked via cookies, and served ads on numerous occasions via retargeting pixels. You may stop temporarily stop historical tracking/cookies by clearing your browser cache. Offline advertising will be done through print mail to customers or through rented mailing list. We never share or sell your information.**

**Security**

**The Company uses a variety of security measures including encryption and authentication to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of your personal information under our control. Registered accounts are secured by your created passwords and the Company takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. The Company uses reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and the Company restricts access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff.**

**Please note that the Company cannot guarantee the security of member account information, no system is 100% secure, especially any which includes transmission of data over the Internet, and unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time.**

**The Company instructs our employees with access to your information that it is to be used only in adherence with the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy and the applicable laws. Employees who misuse customer information are subject to disciplinary action.**

**Choice/Opt-In**

**The Website gives users the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. The Company will never reveal, sell, or make available your email address to anyone for any purpose. The Website also gives users options for removing their information from our database in order to stop receiving our communications. You may continue to receive such communications until our system completes the processing of your request.**

**If at any time you wish to unsubscribe from our mailings, please email us at: [\[email protected\]](https://tactical.stealthops99.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)**

**Links**

**The Website may contain links to other websites and banner ads that take a visitor to another Website. In no case is subscriber information or 'cookies' information provided to the third party Websites. However, please be aware that the Company is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other websites. The Company encourages our users to be aware when they leave this Website and to read the privacy statements of any other website that collects personally identifiable information. On the Internet, many websites do attempt to capture visitor information.**

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

**The Company reserves the right, at our complete discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revised terms on the Website. It is your responsibility to check periodically for any changes the Company may make to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this Website following the posting of changes to these terms or other policies indicates your acceptance of the changes.**

**How to Contact Us**

**If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, Please contact us by emailing us at: [\[email protected\]](https://tactical.stealthops99.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).**

**DETAILED WIRELESS POLICY**

**Data obtained from you in connection with this SMS service may include your name, address, cell phone number, your provider's name, and the date, time, and content of your messages. In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence. All charges are billed by and payable to your mobile service provider. We will not be liable for any delays in the receipt of any SMS messages, as delivery is subject to effective transmission from your network operator. SMS message services are provided on an AS IS basis. We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence. You may opt-out and remove your SMS information by sending "STOP", "END", "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received. If you remove your SMS information from our database it will no longer be used by us for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by us or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you. We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve our technologies and services. We may share aggregated and non personal information with third parties outside of Auction Monster. When we use third parties to assist us in processing your personal information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services. You may remove your information from our database. If you remove your information from our database it will no longer be used by us for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by us or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you. You may remove your information by sending your request in writing via email to [\[email protected\]](https://tactical.stealthops99.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by sending "STOP", "END", "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received.**

**Miscellaneous**

**This Privacy Policy as stated herein constitutes the entire agreement between us with respect to Company’s Privacy Policy.**

**This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Idaho applicable therein, without regard to conflict of laws. You irrevocably consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located in the State of Idaho in connection with any action arising out of or related to these terms of use or their subject matter. You waive any objection based on lack of personal jurisdiction, place of residence, improper venue or forum non-convenience in any such action.**

**If any court having competent jurisdiction holds any provision of this Privacy Policy invalid or unenforceable in any respect, such provision shall be enforced to the maximum extent permitted by law, and the remaining provisions of this Privacy Statement shall continue in full force and effect. No waiver of any provision of this Privacy Policy shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such provision or any other provision of this Privacy Policy.**

**The Money Isn't In the List... It's In The Products That You Sell To Your Email List**

**First, there's no money in the list.** There is only money in the products that you promote, just like the retailer down the street. They are not being paid by simply being open and having customers walk in the door... No, no, no! It's ALL about the products they sell that make the money.

If you are just an affiliate "making money" by wasting money on advertising and getting very little ROI than you have to learn this one secret today.. or your business might be gone tomorrow.

**Fill Out the Form Below To Get Immediate Access**

**Download Free 32 Page Report (.pdf)**

Stealth Ops 99 | Copyright © 2020

Copyright 2015+ All Rights Reserved

Working...
----------
